Library of American Broadcasting Scripts collection
University of Maryland Libraries
- Radio and television Scripts, 1925-1991; 723 items
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/11/1938 (Folder 22.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/29/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/5/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/12/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/19/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 4/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/3/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/10/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/17/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 5/24/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/4/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/18/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 6/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/1/1939 (Folder 25.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's Howdy Folks... No Trouble, 1/1/1939 (Folder 26.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's Howdy Folks... No Trouble, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's Your Own Best Friend, 1/1/1939 (Folder 27.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's Your Own Best Friend, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Danger -- The Key, 8/3/1954 (Folder 28.0)
    - Danger, 8/3/1954 (Item null)
  - David Harding - Counter Spy, 2/16/1947 (Folder 29.0)
    - David Harding - Counter Spy, 2/16/1947 (Item null)
  - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 2/25/1944 (Folder 30.0)
    - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 2/25/1944 (Item null)
  - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 3/17/1944 (Folder 31.0)
    - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 3/17/1944 (Item null)
  - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 7/24/1944 (Folder 32.0)
    - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 7/24/1944 (Item null)
  - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 8/4/1944 (Folder 33.0)
    - Dinnerbell - Managing Your Farm, 8/4/1944 (Item null)
  - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/7/1938 (Folder 34.0)
    - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/7/1938 (Item null)
  - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/11/1938 (Folder 35.0)
    - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/12/1938 (Folder 36.0)
    - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/14/1938 (Folder 37.0)
    - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/14/1938 (Item null)
  - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/29/1938 (Folder 38.0)
    - Don Winslow of the Navy, 7/29/1938 (Item null)
  - Double Trouble, 1/1/1944 (Folder 39.0)
    - Double Trouble, 1/1/1944 (Item null)
  - DX Melody Revue, 3/2/1946 (Folder 40.0)
    - DX Melody Revue, 3/2/1946 (Item null)
  - DX Melody Revue, 3/30/1946 (Folder 41.0)
    - DX Melody Revue, 3/30/1946 (Item null)
  - DX Melody Revue, 4/6/1946 (Folder 42.0)
    - DX Melody Revue, 4/6/1946 (Item null)
  - Eddie Cantor Commercial, 3/16/1952 (Folder 43.0)
    - Eddie Cantor Commercial, 3/16/1952 (Item null)
  - Edward R. Murrow with the News, 1/1/1952 (Folder 44.0)
    - Edward R. Murrow with the News, 1/1/1952 (Item null)
  - Edward, My Son, 6/13/1949 (Folder 45.0)
    - Edward, My Son, 6/13/1949 (Item null)
  - Empire Builders, 4/22/1929 (Folder 46.0)
    - Empire Builders, 4/22/1929 (Item null)
  - Empries of the Moon -- Abraham Lincoln and the Knights of the Golden Circ, 7/3/1938 (Folder 47.0)
    - Empries of the Moon, 7/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Eternal Light -- The Day, 1/22/1956 (Folder 48.0)
    - Eternal Light, 1/22/1956 (Item null)
  - Face the Nation, 1/1/1957 (Folder 49.0)
    - Face the Nation, 1/1/1957 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/8/1935 (Folder 50.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/8/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/15/1935 (Folder 51.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/15/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/29/1935 (Folder 52.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 7/29/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/4/1935 (Folder 53.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/4/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/12/1935 (Folder 54.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/12/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/19/1935 (Folder 55.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/19/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/26/1935 (Folder 56.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 8/26/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/2/1935 (Folder 57.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/2/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/9/1935 (Folder 58.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/9/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/16/1935 (Folder 59.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/16/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/23/1935 (Folder 60.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/23/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/30/1935 (Folder 61.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 9/30/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/7/1935 (Folder 62.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/7/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/14/1935 (Folder 63.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/14/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/21/1935 (Folder 64.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/21/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/28/1935 (Folder 65.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 10/28/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 11/4/1935 (Folder 66.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 11/4/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 11/11/1935 (Folder 67.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 11/11/1935 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 2/17/1936 (Folder 68.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 2/17/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 2/24/1936 (Folder 69.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 2/24/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/2/1936 (Folder 70.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/2/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/6/1936 (Folder 71.0)